http://www.wolfgangsvault.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
(Last Updated on November 19, 2018)
Wolfgang's is committed to protecting your personal security and privacy, and we appreciate your trust that we will uphold this commitment.
This Privacy Policy applies to all websites and web applications ("Sites") which link to this policy and are published by Wolfgang's.
If you have any questions about how we use your personal information, please contact us at privacy@wolfgangs.com
Information we collect
1) Account information. If you decide to create an account and order one of our products or services, we will ask you to provide us with some specific information, for example:
Basic personal details - such as name, delivery address, phone number, and email address;
Log in details - such as username and password;
Payment details - such as your credit card or PayPal account information.
2) Across our Sites you will be presented with the opportunity to sign up for our Newsletters. For this we collect your email address.
If you would like to unsubscribe from our communications at any time, you may do so in the footer of any of our emails. If you would like us to delete your information entirely, or request the information we store about you, please send us an email at privacy@wolfgangs.com. Otherwise, by continuing to interact with our emails, you provide us with permission to manage and use your data as described above.
3) We use cookies and analytics tools across our Sites to collect information about you. This information can be used to improve the performance of the site and enhance your user experience.
If you wish to manage your cookies, please follow the instructions in the "How to manage cookies" section lower on this page.
How we use your information
We collect personal information for the following reasons:
To provide our service - We require some of your basic personal information so our services work as you would expect, for example, delivering your order to your correct address, providing access to our digital content, notifying you of changes to our services and dealing with customer service questions.
To bill our customers - We, along with our authorised payments processors, securely process your payment information to take payments, give refunds and to detect and prevent fraudulent activity. We will also update your payment information in the event that a payment is unsuccessful. You can manage your payment information at any time through the Your Account page on our site, or by contacting customer service.
To communicate with you via our newsletters - We want you to get the most out of our Sites. To do so we offer a Newsletter with carefully-curated special offers, sales and feature announcements. You are able to change your newsletter preferences through the footer of any of our emails.
To improve our Sites - we use cookies to understand how our customers use our Sites and interact with our communications. For example, we use technology on our Sites that records user movements, which pages are most popular, and how navigation options are used. This helps us to identify usability issues and improve the assistance we can provide to users and is also used for aggregated and statistical reporting purposes. We also use cookies to understand what type of device you are using to show you the best version of the site.
Who we share your personal information with
We work with service providers who help to support our business and improve our products. These service providers include, for example, email providers for delivery of our regular newsletters; organisations that host our Sites or databases; and providers of site analytics services. We have contracts in place with these data processors and they can only use your personal information under our instruction. For example, if you subscribe to our newsletters, we will disclose your email address to our distribution partners to facilitate delivery of our newsletter.
How to manage cookies
If you wish to manage your cookies, you can do so via your browser settings. For more information, please visit your browser's help page. Please remember that if you choose to disable cookies, certain sections of our Sites may not work properly.
We use Google Analytics as our primary analytics tool. If you wish to opt out of having cookies placed on your device for Google Analytics you can do so by using Google's opt-out browser add-on, which helps make opting out easy and convenient.
How long we retain your personal information
We retain the majority of your personal information for as long as your account is active and therefore open; this allows you to continue accessing our products and services. If you become inactive - if you do no have an active membership, or have not ordered from us for several years, we may delete elements of the information associated with your account. We will normally warn you if your access is going to be withdrawn and give you the opportunity to retain your account.
Where we don't need to keep all of your information in full, we will obfuscate or aggregate it, primarily in our site activity logs. This is to ensure that we do not retain your information for any longer than is necessary.
Lawful basis for processing
We only process personal information where we have a lawful basis for doing so, such as the following:
User consent – This is where you have given us explicit permission to process personal information for a given purpose. For example, if you subscribe to our newsletters, we ask for your consent before adding your email address to our subscriber list.
Legitimate interest – This is where we have a legitimate interest, as a business, to process personal information. For example, where we are aware of copyright infringements on our Site, it is in our legitimate interests as a business to identify those responsible. We take due care to balance our interests against your right to privacy.
Contractual necessity – This is where we have to process personal information to meet our contractual obligations. For example, if you have ordered a poster from us, we would need to process your delivery address to fulfill your order.
Legal obligation – This is where we have to process personal information in order to comply with the law. For example, we process and retain customer invoice information to comply with U.S. state tax regulations.
How we protect your data
All communications with our Sites, including submission of your email address for Newsletter subscription, is encrypted using SSL (secure sockets layer).
Security / Safe Shopping Guarantee
Protecting the safety of your credit card information is important to us. Ordering from our site is as secure as ordering via a catalog or using your credit card at your favorite restaurant. When you shop from trusted online merchants like us, your online experience should be worry free.
We use SSL (Secure Socket Layering) 128 bit encryption, the standard in Internet encryption technology utilized by other well known online retailers, to protect your information as it travels over the Internet.
Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50 of fraudulent charges made to your credit card. If someone does wrongfully obtain your credit card information because of our failure to properly protect your information and uses this information to incur fraudulent charges and your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50, we will cover the liability for you, up to the full $50.
If you suspect any illegal use of your card, call your issuing bank immediately to make sure your rights are protected.
Contact Us regarding your privacy
Questions regarding this Policy should be directed to privacy@wolfgangs.com. We may also be contacted directly at the following address:
